Hello everyone! This is Harukan Koizumi, aka Oharu!
Hello! Today I would like to explain about our new single
I would like to explain about our new single "LOVE!
Let's go today! Let's go!
Ear ear ear ear ear ear ear!
Yes, that's right, we, Chotokimeki Advertising Department's 3rd single
Love Iya Iya Jikki was released on the 10th of May!
It's rare that we have been making videos during the month of May!
We've been shooting a lot of amazing videos and editing them.
I've been editing and storing all kinds of videos.
but this time, I'm going to do it right.
But this time, I'm going to make it right.
I've been shooting in May, just in time.
And it's so hot!
In summer, I don't turn on the air conditioner and close the windows.
I don't have a cold or anything.
I feel like it's been a while since I've been on YouTube
I feel like it's been a while.
I'm worried about the sweat on my nose.
Don't worry about it.
Please take it easy on me.
I'd like to digress a little bit.
I'd like to explain about the Love Ya-Ya family.
Have you listened to it yet?
Yes, this song is about the super time war.
Call me more...
I need you to love me more
I need you to love me more and more
It's a song that exploded with the desire for approval.
This song is a song about the desire for approval.
It's a song that takes that need for approval and puts it in a very positive light.
So, you know...
In the song, there are a lot of lyrics that say, "If you don't give me love
There are a lot of lyrics that say "I don't like it if you don't give me love".
I don't like it when you don't celebrate our anniversary more.
I don't like it when you don't contact me more.
It's a song about a girl's selfishness.
I think this song has a lot of girls' selfishness in it.
And then there are these
Six lovely angels singing it.
Six lovely angels singing the song.
That's right, everyone.
You have to pay more attention to us.
You have to love us more.
It's a song that says, "You have to love us more.
When I first heard this song
I thought the title "Love Iya Iya Iya House
I had a very strange image of what kind of song it was.
I was imagining what kind of song it would be.
I was imagining what kind of song it would be, but I thought it would be one of the best songs
I had never heard a song like this before.
It's like a normal song, like J-Pop or something.
I've never heard this song before.
I thought it was a song I had never heard before.
That's why it's so outstanding.
I don't think there are really many songs
I think there really aren't many songs about a house that you don't want to live in.
I think there aren't many songs that sing about a house without earphones.
So it's a song with a lot of personality.
I really felt it was a song with a lot of personality.
What did you think when you first heard it?
The choreography is really cute.
It's easy to imitate.
It's like, "Give me love or else I won't love you.
The catchy melody and choreography
I think it's an exquisite match.
This song, too.
Sako Makiida, who choreographed "Gyutto" and "I love you"...
Sako Makita, who choreographed "Gyutto" and "Suki wo Suki", choreographed the choreography for this song.
The choreography is really cute!
1...
Iya Iya Iya Iya 2
Iya Iya Iya 4
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll never forgive you for cheating on me.
It's amazing.
It's just like Mr. Makiida.
Every time you put on a cute choreography
That's how I feel.
And this time, my hair is in a ponytail.
I'm wearing it in a ponytail.
I'm still wearing a ponytail.
It's a little bit high ponytail.
Today it's a little lower.
I put it in a higher ponytail.
So that you can see the hair ornament.
It's a little bit like a princess ponytail.
I've been wearing my hair in a ponytail lately.
I've been wearing my bangs in a bun.
Today, I parted it a little.
It's like...
My best friend says she likes it that way, so I just go with it.
Which do you guys prefer? Do you have parted bangs or not? Or do you not?
Or do you separate them like today?
Or do you have the bangs like today's? Like this.
I think I usually wear my bangs a little straighter like this, but which do you guys prefer?
And that costume has a lot of upside-down hearts on it.
And also pastel-colored costume with lots of hearts and ribbons.
And did you guys notice? It's lavishly signed, and it says "To Oharu-chan" on it.
It says "To Oharu-chan." Julian wrote this for me.To Oharu-chan" is written on it. Julian wrote this for me.
I wrote this on her head with ribbons and hearts, and she's so cute!
How can she make such a pretty face?
She's a different person. She's adorable.
And there's also a coupling song for "Love in My Earliest Years" and "I'll Never Let You Down" and a live video of the Makuhari concert.
I'm sure most of you have already purchased the album.
I'm sure most of you have already purchased it, so please continue to check it out!
From here, I'd like to talk about what you like about Love Iya-Ya-Ya.
De-den! Oharu-chan's "I just love you too much" and then Julian's "I just love you too much" are the best!
Anyway, I like you too much!
That's the part called "Suki"!
Julian's "suki" was originally a kind of "I like you too much" part, like a calm woman's kind of thing.
But when we were recording, he said "I like you so much" and "I like you so much" and "I like you so much" and "I like you so much" and "I like you so much.
But when we were recording the song, we tried different patterns for the six of us, and finally the best one was the one we used, so they used that one.
The choreography is cute, too.
The way Sakai-san says "Hello" and Hiyori says "Hello" in the second verse are so cute!
The "Lifecycle Mini Game" is the part where you say "Hello" and "I'm going to ask you to go on a date with me every time.
When I was recording that part, Hiyori was winning a little bit, but when I asked her about it, she said, "Can you go above me?
I was asked if I could go over the top, but I couldn't.
I couldn't. Hiyori was the winner.
I think Hello is cute, and I think that Hito-chan, in the process of creating this Love Year influence, really cut her hair too much.
Hito-chan cut her bangs too short.
When Hito-chan was saying "I cut my bangs too much, what should I do?
The staff was doing a rat play, and they put the word "I cut my bangs too short" in the lyrics out of the several possible lyrics.
You know...
What's with that episode?
The part where Oharu crosses the stage in a flash... that's from the music video.
There were the most people who liked this scene of Oharu cutting across.
Why?
Why? It's so strange.
Why so many? I was just wondering.
Well, of course I'm happy.
But even from Oharu's family, it's like the part where you cross the street is the best part of the show for you.
There? Like that.
Every time... they ask me to cut out the lip scene.
I've been trying to get them to take lots of pictures of the lip scene.
Why the part where you're crossing the street? I don't know.
And Hiyori's green tea swirling...
I honestly wondered why that was the most common scene.
But thank you very much!
I'm a little surprised at the number of comments on this one, but...
Yes...
Thank you for the perfect wink from Oharu.
I think she winks a lot, maybe 2 or 3 times in the music video for this song.
Your outfit is just so cute!
The earrings and necklace are also included this time!
I'm a little happy to be able to wear a necklace like the one I used to adore when I was a kid.
It's like a dream come true!
I also love the fabric of the skirt with the upside-down hearts.
I also love the fabric of the upside-down heart.
It's like a towel.
That's a compliment.
The way everyone dances after saying, "If you cheat on me, I'll never forgive you!
Thank you very much.
That was amazing!
That's the only part of the song where the dancing is really good.
I'd say the chorus and this kick-ass part.
Yeah, that's the part where this pose comes out a lot.
The point is that it's upside down.
The point is to put your fingers on the side.
That's the point.
I love the instrumentation, it's very fun, very exciting, and very varied.
I'm very excited about that Love Iyaki single.
Also, the instrumental is included in the subs, so please listen to a lot of the background sounds.
Please try to listen to a lot of the background sounds!
I love Norano who can't really get excited!
I can't really get excited about it.
Yeah, I've been working on this since we were recording it.
I've been wishing I had a part in this song since it was recorded.
I really like the back-riding feeling of this song.
I wonder what it's like to be able to sing this song with such rock 'n' roll feeling...
But you know, I'm having so much fun singing.
I'm having so much fun singing that I'm really not excited to go out.
But every time I sing, I do it with a smile on my face.
That's my goal for the future.
If I can work on my singing voice and facial expression a little more
I'd like to study a little more about my singing voice and facial expression.
I enjoy the live performance and the singing part.
I sing with a smile on my face.
The part where Koizumi-san is vacuuming.
Yes, I'm vacuuming too.
When he says, "Oh no, no, no, I want to be bothered with you more!
It's so strong!
I know... it's a little bit harsh.
It makes my ears happy every time I hear it.
I love it when she says she can't work hard because she's too spooked out to do it once a week or something.
The lyrics are so cute and Hiyori says it's her favorite lyric every time.
Hiyori says it's her favorite lyric every time.
Kanami's giggling is too cute!
Yeah, this time Kanamin is wearing half-twin...
Kanamin is so bubbly and bubbly.
Kanamin is so cute and bubbly.
It's like when your mother spoils you.
There's a picture of her expression when she was really spoiled by her mother.
It's like the face of a child who is happy when his mother praises him.
It's a compliment, but it's so cute.
It's so cute and it makes me think, "Wow, he's cute!
Kaname is almost 24 years old.
You can't tell that at all. She's like a 3-year-old.
But lately I've been getting calls like I'm 3 or 5 or 8 years old.
I don't know why.I don't know why.
The Tettechi pose of "Please spoil me more" is too cute!
What's Tecchi Pose?
This time, the choreography is full of cats in poses like this or this or this.
Yes, there are a lot of cats in the choreography.
There are poses with cats jumping and yan-yaning.
And there will be a lot of hearts.
Stick out your heart.
I won't forgive you for looking where you're going... if you're a bad boy.
Here's a cat, too.
And there will be a lot of cats and hearts.
So many cats and hearts will come out
So many cats and hearts!
So please imitate me and dance!
The final pose is cute!
Hey, if you get it, answer me, Chan!
I wonder if this is also a signature pose.
I want you to wink your right eye in the choreography.
Please do it with me!
I'm really bad at winking with my right eye.
If you understand, please answer me.
So this is how it goes.
Hito-chan's first chorus, "Give me love...
the part where the little "love" is in the chorus.
The song was arranged by Muteki who wrote the song this time.
Hito-chan imitated the way Muteki sang.
Hito-chan imitated Muteki's way of singing.
I guess it was like no one else was in the song but Hito-chan.
That's why I thought it was different.
From "Where are you looking?
I liked the dance where they were fighting with each other in the "I'm going to punish you" scene.
I want JKs to imitate it and dance to it.
What are you looking at?
I'd be happy if we could get them to dance like this in groups.
I'd be very happy.
The people around you can do whatever they want.
You can do whatever you want.
And anything else is fine, so please dance.
Young people, please!
You don't have to be young.
I'm counting on you.
Even if you don't understand, you'll want to say "Hi!
Hachitaro, if you know what I'm talking about, please answer me.
Oh, I'm so happy!
If you know what I'm talking about, say hi!
Everyone, say hi!
And if they ask you to say you like them...
You have to say "I love you.
Your moves are so cute!
I've been having so much fun since I saw them at Hibiya.
I'm looking forward to seeing them grow up.
I mean it's fun to grow up
This song was the last time we had a fine spring
We performed it at Hibiya Open-Air Concert Hall
It was really great to see how well you all handled it.
There's a special YouTube video of the live performance.
I was so impressed by the way you were able to get the calls in your head.
So please continue to call out a lot!
That's right!
It was made to be easy to call, so even if it's your first time, you can get really excited!
The first performance at Hibiyano was amazing!
So I personally want to do it at festivals and stuff.
Yes, I'm thinking of doing it at festivals.
The choreography of the too-cut bangs
It's not for bangs that have been cut a little too short.
Take me to the phone hello
Yes, yes.
It's got some kind of rap-like lyrics, and it's really good, too.
Aki-chan sings.
Do you really care about me?
I think it's so cute!
I love the choreography here.
Julia wrapping the pasta so much!
It's a music video, isn't it?
Yes, she's wrapping the pasta so much!
That's funny, and I wanted to eat that.
I like the choreography of the pose of 1,2,3 and the vertical swaying.
Chachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachacha!
I really hope you guys like me more on social media or something.
I want you to like me more on social media or something.
I don't want you to like me more.
You guys have to take a good look at it.
The part where everyone hates it.
Yes, we all hate it.
I like that the songs are short because it's fresh.
Oh, yes, including coupling songs.
Most of the songs are less than 3 minutes long.
It's so easy to listen to.
When Mr. B, the promoter, recommends it to his friends, they think it's the first time they've heard this idol.
It's the first time for me to listen to an idol song, and I think it's easy to listen to.
I think it's easy to listen to if it's only 3 minutes long.
I think it's a good opportunity for you to start with a short song.
Start with a short song.
I'm sure you'll get hooked on Kisensen.
I'd be happy if you get hooked.
Yes, I'm sure...
The lyrics are too cute!
Thank you
Ponytail Oharu
I'm glad to hear that your ponytail is so popular.I'm glad to hear that your ponytail was so well received.
Aki-chan told me she liked my ponytail too.
I was so happy!
Your dance is the cutest!
Thank you so much!
There are so many cute parts in the dance.
I hope you can find a lot of cute parts
I hope you can find a lot of cute parts and imitate them.
I'm glad you liked the call song.
I'm glad to hear that.
The call ban has been lifted from the spring festival.
I'll be happy if everyone shouts a lot
I'll be happy if everyone shouts a lot and gets excited a lot.
Love Iyayuki from now on!
Watch and listen to more and more
Please enjoy more and more!
If you don't enjoy it
I hate it!
If you liked today's video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel.
If you enjoyed today's video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
See you soon!
Bye bye!